https://www.jazzcorner.com/privacy_policy.php

HomeRosterPodcastsNewsLogin / Create AccountNewsJukeboxShopContact
JazzCorner.com is the largest portal for the official websites of hundreds of jazz musicians and organizations.
New features on JazzCorner include the jazz video share where you can upload and share jazz and blues videos, JazzCorner Jukebox, surf the net with Jazz always on, submit your latest jazz news, and check out what's hot at JazzCorner's Speakeasy, the busiest bulletin board for jazz.
Be the first to know where Jazz artists are performing in our gigs section, and be sure to listen to our podcasts with established and up and coming jazz musicians in our Innerviews section.
JazzCornerRoster:
ArrangerBassBen WolfeChris WalkerDave
HollandNat ReevesRay DrummondRufus ReidBig BandsCharles TolliverDave
HollandBlogsAcrylic Jazz Art Paintings Ben WolfeCary GoldbergClark TerryCold Jazz Consilience Productions Elements of Jazz Eli YaminEye Shot Jazz Freddie
BryantFree Jazz Improvised Blog In A Mellow Tone Jazz Beyond Jazz Jazz Chronicles Jazz Ink Jazz Insights Jazz Lives Jazz Observer Jazz Station Jazz Wax Jazz@Rochester Jessica JonesKen FrancklingLarry
AppelbaumLeterland London Jazz
Lubricity Mark WeinsteinMark PolishookPhil BowlerReflection in Rhythm The Independent Ear The Jazz Breakfast The Jazz Cat BookingBroadcastersBob BernotasOpen Sky Jazz CampsNew York Jazz Workshop Roberto Ocasio Foundation CelloConsultingMarty AshbyMitchell Feldman Associates Open Sky Jazz DrumsBobby SanabriaChris
ParkerTerri Lyne CarringtonEducationJazz Museum in Harlem Jazz Power
New York Jazz Workshop Thelonious Monk Institute Westchester Center for Jazz & Contemporary Music EventsInternational Jazz Day FestivalsPittsburgh International Jazz Fest FilmMartino Unstrung FluteGaea SchellLew TabackinMark WeinsteinGroupsBand of Bones New York Voices GuitarFreddie BryantGene EssJoe CarterLee RitenourLew WoodallMark KleinhautMarty AshbyHarmonicaGrégoire MaretManagementLVanHart Productions McKenna Group Productions OrganGreg LewisOrganizationsJazz Foundation of America Jazz Museum in Harlem Louis Armstrong Educational Foundation New York Jazz Workshop Open Sky Jazz Thelonious Monk Institute Westchester Center for Jazz & Contemporary Music PercussionJoe McCarthyJulian GerstinPianoBob RodriguezBrandon GoldbergCliff KormanDave BurrellDebbie PoryesDena DeRoseEli YaminEzra
WeissGaea SchellGeorge CablesGreg McKenzieJames WeidmanJawanza KobieJimmy AmadieJoanne BrackeenJonny KingKenny BarronLiz MagnesMichael WolffMichele RosewomanRenee RosnesRob SchneidermanRonny WhyteSteve KuhnProducingLee RitenourMarty AshbyTodd BarkanPublicityMitchell Feldman Associates PublishingMJQ Music, Inc. Radio PromotionGroov Marketing & Consulting Mitchell Feldman Associates Record CompaniesJoken Records JSL Records Sharp Nine Records Recording StudiosAvatar Studios SaxophoneBobby
WatsonChico FreemanChris GreeneGary SmulyanJoey
BerkleyJohn
RichmondLew TabackinRalph LalamaSteve
WilsonTromboneChris WashburneClifton AndersonDavid ChamberlainMatt HavilandRobin EubanksSteve DavisSteve
TurreTrumpetAhmed AbdullahCharles TolliverChris PasinClark TerryRandy Brecker TubaVibesCecilia SmithDave ShankMatthias LupriVocalsAmy LondonAva LoganChris WalkerDena DeRoseDenise
ThimesGiacomo GatesJosephine LivotiJudi SilvanoLainie CookeLibby YorkLisa SokolovNancy HarrowNew York Voices Ronny WhyteSusie MeissnerSusie MeissnerWritersBob BernotasWillard Jenkins
About JazzCorner:
History
Contact Us
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
We understand your need to maintain your privacy when using the Internet for your communication, shopping, exploration, and play. To make sure you understand our approach to online privacy issues, please read this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use to enhance and understand your experience at JazzCorner®.com
We ask you for your personal information when you sign up for our mailing list, when you make a purchase, download music, participate in any community features, or enter a contest or sweepstakes. We also may ask you various questions about your interests or preferences. We use this information to personalize Jazzcorner.com for you, to inform you about or offer you new features or services customized to your preferences, for marketing purposes, to contact you about your purchases, or to notify you if you have won a prize or contest.
What information do we collect?
The information we collect falls into one of two categories - personally identifiable information and aggregated information. Personally identifiable information is information that can be used to identify you. Aggregated information is information that is not associated with a specific user, but instead anonymous information on many users, such as the number of visitors to the Site in a month's time. We collect personally identifiable information (such as name, email, residence address, whenever you voluntarily submit it to the Site, make a purchase or participate in our online activities. Examples of information that you submit voluntarily include: when you make a purchase, answer our polls, enter our contests, fill out the registration page, send us feedback, download music, or post in our message board, fill out a survey, participate on JazzCorner's VideoShare.
If you register, we might also ask you about your musical preferences or other information to customize the Site for you. You always have the option of choosing not to reveal this personally identifiable information to us.
In addition, we collect and store statistics and other information about the online activities of our visitors on an aggregated (collective) basis. For example, we track the number of people who view each page, the order in which pages are viewed, and other information to learn which features are the most popular and to refine our design and marketing efforts.
How do we use the personal information we collect?
JazzCorner.com uses both aggregated and personally identifiable information to operate and enhance our sites and to enhance your experience by displaying content and marketing messages that we believe will be of interest to you.
We do not sell your personally identifiable information to third parties. We also do not share your personally identifiable information with third parties unless they need to provide you with prizes and services you acknowledge.
We ONLY use the personal information we collect to communicate with you, to deliver purchases, to notify you if you've won a prize for a contest that you've entered, to assist you in your JazzCorner.com online experience, or to be able to personalize a part of the site with the services and information you choose. If you choose to subscribe to our newsletter, we use your personal information to select and deliver messages to you.
JazzCorner.com uses aggregated information to sell and deliver advertising. We disclose aggregated information about our Site to third parties, including information regarding the effectiveness of our advertisers' advertisements.
Please, remember, information you provide as part of your community Profile of preferences (User Profiles) is not confidential, and is accessible by the public. Similarly, any information you provide in chat rooms, message boards, or other public forums is not confidential and we may not remind you, so please keep this in mind if you're going to use these parts of our Site. Your choice to disclose personally identifiable information in such cases is up to you.
How can you change or correct the personal information you provided to us?
You can contact us at lois@jazzcorner.com to request changes to your basic user information.
What about cookies?
Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to your computer's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies can make the Web more useful by storing information about your preferences on a particular site. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and many major websites use them to provide
useful features for their users. Cookies in and of themselves do not personally identify users, although they do identify a user's computer. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you'd prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies. However, you may not be able to take full advantage of all the features JazzCorner.com has to offer.
We use cookies or IP addresses for a number of uses, including helping us to tailor a website or a marketing message to better match your needs and interests, and to allow us to better understand how users use our Site. You are always free to instruct your web browser to decline our cookies if it has the capability to do so, but some parts of our Site may not work properly if you do.
Choice/Opt-Out
JazzCorner and all it's affiliate and hosted websites provide users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us. This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. Please send email to lois@jazzcorner.com or write us at:
The AudioWorks Group, Ltd
70 West 95th St #3F
New York, NY 10025
Email Address:
HOME :: ROSTER :: PODCASTS :: NEWS :: JUKEBOX :: SHOP :: CONTACT
History :: Contact Us :: Privacy Policy
© 1996-2020 JazzCorner
